ROBERT MOORE

Clawson, MI, 48017 · (989)387-0158 · Contact me: Email · LinkedIn · GitHub

As a Learning Management System Architect, I specialize in effective communication, system administration, and platform governance with a focus on data integrity. Driven to improve and use technology to optimize every aspect of the work environment where the most impact can be found. I have experience with developing, leading, and implementing projects from basic ideas to fully functional processes leveraging any resource available.

EXPERIENCE

ROCKET CENTRAL - DETROIT, MI

LEARNING MANAGEMENT SYSTEM ARCHITECT JUNE 2023 – CURRENT

Define and identify our current learning ecosystem capabilities to leverage in vendor communications as well as guide internal solution discussions.

- Served as interim team leader for 9 months while transitioning to a new work tracking platform
- Consistently act as subject matter expert consulting on system capabilities to teams across numerous business areas
- Use system architecture diagramming to identify risk points and opportunities for new solutions
- Focus on cross-platform integrations enabling data driven learning recommendation
- Adapted internal processes to remove extraneous vendors saving over \$500,000 annually

SENIOR LEARNING MANAGEMENT SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR NOVEMBER 2022 – JUNE 2023

Strategized primary focus areas for the team to focus on and opted into becoming the primary contact point between most team vendor tools and the larger business area.

- Regularly presented complex system business cases to Leadership to generate buy-in on focused team effort
- Developed auditing processes for external vendors leading to 50-300% increase in engaged user counts per platform
- Reconfigured / Implemented a single SSO provider to align all platforms to a single vendor
- Built low-code solutions to solve root-cause problems, saving up to 10 hours per week of data transformation efforts

LEARNING MANAGEMENT SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR NOVEMBER 2020 – MAY 2022

Maintained and optimized the Learning Management System utilized to administer as well as track all training across Rocket Companies.

- Review, communicate and led team on product updates and releases
- Mentored coworkers to level up system skills and apply company standards
- Regularly released trainings to audiences of 25,000+ team members
- Generated reporting on system functionality, auditing records, and training metrics to all business area senior leaders

EDUCATION

GRAND CIRCUS – DETROIT, MI
C# .NET FULL STACK BOOTCAMP OCT 2024

OAKLAND UNIVERSITY – ROCHESTER, MI
HUMAN RESOURCE DEVELOPMENT B.S. DEC 2019

SKILLS

- SQL / Angular / REST APIs
- C# / .NET
- HTML/CSS / Javascript
- Saba LMS
- Storyline / RISE / Captivate authoring tools
- Agile project management

- Mentorship / Leadership
- Microsoft Power Suite
- Vendor communication and management
- System integration and optimization
- Technical demonstration and presentation
- Troubleshooting and root-cause analysis